# KAYLA LAZRAK

### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Efficient, outgoing Bachelor of Fine Arts graduate with an appreciation of artistic achievement. Enhances gallery experiences to increase patron loyalty. Excellent organizational and communications skills with expertise in supporting diverse gallery operations. Organized and dependable candidate successful at managing multiple priorities with a positive attitude. Willingness to take on added responsibilities to meet team goals.

### **SKILLS**

- Adobe Suite Experience, particularly Photoshop and Illustrator
- Microsoft Office Certified
- Experience installing and striking art exhibitions
- Years of customer service
- Team worker
- Reliable

### **WORK HISTORY**

### ASSISTANT GALLERIST 07/2023 - Current

Canary Gallery, Birmingham, AL

- Handled incoming works of art and prepared for exhibitions and packaged outgoing pieces for safe transport
- Coordinated private and public gallery events
- Greeted visitors of gallery and ensured an enjoyable atmosphere to admire the artworks, giving art and artist information as requested
- Built relationships with customers to encourage repeat business.

## ART LAB GALLERY ASSISTANT 09/2021 to 04/2022

**UAB Department of Art and Art History**, Birmingham, AL

- Assisted in installing and striking exhibitions held in Art Lab gallery, including The Salon, Progress in Practice, Death and Transformation, two art history major capstone presentations, and Out with the Fire by Sloss Metal Arts
- Worked with artists to ensure exhibitions were correct
- Supervised artwork at AEIVA Museum for 2022 Juried Student Exhibition
- Gave tours and information to introspective art students

### CASHIER/FRONT SERVICE CLERK 01/2016 to 01/2018

Publix, Pelham, AL

- Provided excellent customer service and assisted in maintaining cleanliness of store
- Handled cash, operated terminal and maintained a high level of cleanliness at register
- Assisted customers at checkout, scanning and bagging groceries
- Helped customers to their car

### **EDUCATION**

**University of Alabama at Birmingham**, Birmingham, AL **Bachelor of Fine Arts**, 04/2023

Summa Cum Laude Distinguished Honors UAB Provost Scholarship Recipient 3.92 GPA

Classes taken gave proficient knowledge in: Adobe Suite, Art History, written and verbal communication skills

### **LANGUAGES**

### **French**

**Professional Working**